I had a rear end collision
and my friend told me about Phyllis and I, so I came over
and I had $18,000 worth of damage on my car.
It was only like about a year and a half old.
So when I came here,
they opened up the hood once they got all the parts off
and it was another $3,000 worth of damage.
And they replaced everything, brand new, genuine four parts.
And this is during COVID when the supply chain was real
slow, but these guys fixed it like it was brand new.
I turned my brother onto this place.
My, the girl that cuts my hair, she came here for her
and a couple of my buddies, they came here.
So these guys, they know a lot about the insurance business.
These guys are great. I would tell anybody to come here.
I called them up and they had all the answers for me.
They said, we got this part ordered.
It was a real mess, but they figured it out.
And I would come here any, anytime I got,
I had a couple fender benders with the same car
and I brought here Ed Junior.
He's will buff it out. No. And they didn't even charge me.
So it was great.